(Amy:)I have spent my life in
pursuit of pure knowledge.
(Amy:)Until I met you,
my decisions
(Amy:)were founded in
logic and reason.
(Amy:)And yet here I stand before you,
130 pounds of raging estrogen,
(Amy:)longing to grab hold
of your gluteus maximus
(Amy:)and make Shakespeare's
metaphorical
(Amy:)beast with two backs.
(Zack:)My gluteus what?
(Amy:)On the other hand,
(Amy:)as I look at the blank, ape-like
expression on your face,
(Amy:)I have decided to adopt the
Vulcan practice of Kolinar.
(Amy:)Good-bye, Zack.
Bye.
(Amy:)Hoo.
(Zack:)That should hold me for a while.
(Howard:)I'm legally obligated
to inform you
(Howard:)that I took a karate lesson
when I was 11.
(Howard:)I'd be a regular ninja by now